

ABDULLAH RAHIN

WEB DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Hello, I am Rahin. I am a hard-working and passionate web designer and web developer with 3+ years of experience. I am highly focused on my work and completed each project as per the given schedule.believe in learning and developing new skills every day to have a successful future ahead. My main intent is to pleasure the client with my efficiency & efforts, and keep a positive rapport throughout the projects and the connection.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Backend Developer at Shikbe Shobai 2021 - 2023

I did work at Shikbe Shobai as a backend developer in For the last 2 years. I did work at as a backend developer with PHP & Laravel, and JavaScript. I gather lots of experience & knowledge from here.

Web Design & Development at Upwork & Fiverr 2021 - Present

I am working in Upwork & Fiverr as a Web
Designer & Developer with expertise WordPress |
PHP & Laravel and also did many local clients
projects.

CONTACT

+88 018-874-97149

ahmedrahin660@gmail.com

nirpur-14, Dhaka

https://aarahin.com/resume

EDUCATION

Feni Collage

2019 - 2021 Higher Secondary School Certificate (H.S.C)

2021 - Present Bachelor's of Business Studies (BBS)

Dhaka Commerce College

SKILLS

- PSD to HTML
- CSS, CSS3
- JavaScript
- WordPress
- PHP
- Laravel
- MySQL

Web Designer & Laravel Developer

2023 - Present

Now I'm working with a team. From there I'm constantly working as a skilled web developer with a new experience.

CERTIFICATIONS

Full-stack Web Development

Shikbe Shobai

I completed my full-stack web development .through this course, I got familiar with web technology. I made myself proficient in HTML, CSS, WordPress, Javascript, and PHP.

PHP & Laravel

Shikbe Shobai

For strong backend knowledge, and to make yourself more efficient in PHP & most popular framework Laravel, I did complete that course.

WordPress Theme Development

Codeman BD

I developed myself as a good wordpress developer through this course.

More Information About Me:











- Figma to WordPress
- Github
- Wix
- WordPress Theme Development
- Microsoft Office

REFERENCE

FAISAL HAMID HIMEL

Mentor, Shikbe Shobai +01715-234605 faisal.hamid.hemel.1992@gmail.com

GAZI WAFA

Mentor, Shikbe Shobai +01814-294661 gaziwafa65@gmail.com